<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vigor Lanka</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Home">Home</string>
    <string name="People">People</string>
    <string name="Contact_us">"contact us "</string>

    <string name="content_home_black_pepper">Our Sri Lankan black pepper has a quick bite and a lingering aroma. We select only high density, early harvest berries deep black in color. We can provide any quantity with your requirements.</string>
    <string name="content_home_red_pepper">Sri Lankan Roasted Chili Powder’s deep rich aroma and natural flavor will make your meal truly Sri Lankan. Roasted Chili Powder are prepared from toasting Sri Lankan dried chilies and then grinding them to release their potent flavor. </string>
    <string name="content_home_cinnamon">"True" cinnamon is native to the island of Sri Lanka, formerly called Ceylon, just south of the Indian subcontinent. In fact, this cinnamon is sometimes referred to as Ceylon cinnamon, and is prized for its delicate flavor. </string>
    <string name="content_home_tumeric">"Organic turmeric powder comes from a region in Sri Lanka, where the curcumin content is north of 5%. High quality turmeric is high in essential oils and curcumin, which gives turmeric its unique orange-yellow coloring. Turmeric powder adds a complex, rich, woody flavor to Indian curries, "</string>
    <string name="content_home_cummin">"Cumin is used in virtually every cuisine that is or has ever been. Our fine Sri Lankan cumin is warm, nutty and slightly hot, with lemon and bitter tones. It brings our sweet flavors in food and is great in chili, curries, stews and soups."</string>
    <string name="content_home_tea_powder">"Sri Lanka is one of the world's most significant exporters of orthodox teas because of the sheer volume grown and exported. The island now known as Sri Lanka was historically referred to as “Ceylon” by the British colonial powers, hence the name for Ceylon teas. "</string>
    <string name="content_home_packag_shipping">"We can export any quantity of products with your requirments as boxes, 20ft and 40ft etc. Firstly you can give the requirment and will offer you a quatation. If you want any sample we can ship first then you can place your order. Please see the contact section."</string>

    <string-array name="contact_reason">
        <item>Quotation Request</item>
        <item>General Request</item>
        <item>Order Request</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>